

# Glendon **Grapperhaus**

Software Engineer

- (314) 960-7018
- ▼ glendonray.com
- Saint Louis, Missouri

#### SUMMARY

Full stack engineer with over ten years of experience in creating beautiful websites. Proficient in translating designs into pixel-perfect user interfaces, lending to wonderful user experiences. Excellent soft skills with a love for communicating and collaborating with a team.

## EXPERIENCE

Senior Web Developer 09/2020 - 02/2024

Atomicdust <sup>对</sup>

Built, managed, and updated websites for clients using Wordpress, PHP, SQL, Javascript, JQuery, HTML, and CSS/SCSS.

- Translated award winning designs and mockups into pixel-perfect user interfaces and user experiences.
- · Advised designers, project managers, and account managers on questions regarding the technology stack to help communicate requirements to clients and make accurate estimates.
- Helped a client migrate over 10,000 rows of data, spanning posts, events, pages, glossary terms, and data points, and reformatted it to work in a new CMS and layout.
- Updated development stack to allow for the use of new build tools, increasing build speed and efficiency by 25%.
- Delivered customized CMS layouts to clients needs, creating intuitive editing experiences for users.

**Web Developer** 06/2017 - 09/2020

Falk Harrison 7

- Developed websites using Wordpress, PHP, SQL, Javascript, JQuery, HTML, and CSS/SCSS.
- · Communicated with clients to understand their needs and translating them into customized content management systems and dynamic websites.
- Built a custom templated solution for the digital version of client's bi-annual publications while preserving brand elements.
- Maintained client websites on both scheduled and as-needed basises, updating their tools and troubleshooting errors or compatibility issues.
- Audited client websites to help maximize their accessibility, speed, SEO, and security.

**Web Developer** 02/2015 - 06/2017

- Created and maintained websites for clients using Wordpress, PHP, SQL, Javascript, JQuery, HTML, and CSS.
- Programmed and managed the rebuild of yellowdogllc.com.
- Designed, built, and keyframed web animations, enhancing user engagement and visual appeal.

### EDUCATION

Interactive Media and Web Design

08/2010 - 05/2014

Lindenwood University - Bachelor of Arts (BA)

# SKILLS

React

Javascript MySQL  $\mathsf{HTML}$ 

PHP CSS/SCSS